sbicapsec.com 2008-09-28

# | Welcome to SBICAP Securities |

|  |   
---  
| 

|  ** Latest News**  
---  
|   |   |    
---|---|---  
  |  |    
  |  |    
  
  |  |  | 

SBICAP Securities Ltd (SSL), does not collect personal information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personal information may be gathered for the registration process for services and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., message boards), suggestions, etc. Personal information on individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties unless:-

|    
---|---  
  |    
  
  * The information is provided to help complete a transaction initiated by you; 
  * You request or authorize it; 
  * The disclosure is required by/or directed by law; or 
  * You have been informed about the possibility of such disclosure for marketing or similar purposes through a prior communication and have been given the opportunity to decline

|    
  
Users should be aware that SSL may permit third parties to offer their services through its site. SSL is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the privacy policies of such third party when providing personally identifiable information.

|   
|   
  
Users should also be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of SSL internet servers or through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements. Users are also being made aware that SSL cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by third parties hosting data for SSL. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; Users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features available from SSL.  
SSL reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

|   
|   |   |    
---|---|---  
**1.** | **How we keep customer information accurate** |    
  | 

It is in your interest, and it is our objective, for us to have accurate, current, and complete information concerning you and your accounts. We have strict procedures that our employees abide by to meet this objective. While some procedures are required by Central, State laws or RBI regulations, we have implemented additional procedures to maintain accurate, current, and complete financial information, including processes to update information and remove outdated information. If you believe that we have incorrect information about you or your accounts, please email us through the feedback mechanism provided on the website or modify the profile information on the site as permissible. We will correct any erroneous information as quickly as possible. 

|    
  |   |    
**2.** | **How we limit access to customer information by our employees** |    
  | We have procedures that limit access to personally identifiable information to those employees with a business reason for knowing such information about you. We educate our employees on their responsibility to protect the confidentiality of customer information, and hold them accountable if they violate this privacy policy.  |    
  |   |    
**3.** | **Our security procedures to protect customer information** |    
  | We follow best security practices to help prevent unauthorized access to confidential information about you. |    
  |   |    
**4.** | **How we restrict the disclosure of customer information** |    
  | 

SBI does not release customer information except as directed by law or as per your mandate. We do not share specific information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data with nonaffiliated third parties for their independent use unless:

|    
  | 

  * The information is provided to help complete a transaction initiated by you; 
  * You request or authorize it; 
  * The disclosure is required by/or directed by law; or 
  * You have been informed about the possibility of such disclosure for marketing or similar purposes through a prior communication and have been given the opportunity to decline

|    
  |   |    
**6.** | 

**Disclosing our privacy commitment to you we want you to understand our commitment to personal privacy and have formulated this privacy policy. This privacy policy is provided to:**

|    
  | 

  * A potential customer who inquires about our products and services or who would like a copy of our privacy policy 
  * A customer who has established a relationship with us 
  * A potential customer who has applied for a loan 
  * A visitor to SBI's web site 

|    
  |   |
